kadenze.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Kadenze

#### Last Updated August 21, 2014

This notice describes Kadenze Inc.’s ("Company" or "Kadenze") privacy policy (referred to as "Privacy Policy" or "Policy") and applies to Company’s proprietary learning environment platform (referred to as the "PLE Service" or "KADENZE"). This Privacy Policy applies to you, as a User of the PLE Service and as an end user of the User Submissions provided by Users of the PLE Service. 

PLEASE REVIEW THIS PRIVACY POLICY BEFORE USING THE PLE SERVICE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH OUR PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE PLE SERVICE. BY USING THE PLE SERVICE OR SUBMITTING ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION OR CONTENT TO THE PLE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. Your use of the PLE Service is also subject to the KADENZE Terms of Use. Please review the KADENZE Terms of Use, located at www.kadenze.com/terms_and_conditions for additional details regarding your use of the PLE Service. All capitalized terms have the same meaning as defined in the KADENZE Terms of Use unless otherwise stated herein. 

### Registration

During the registration process, you may be required to provide certain information and you will establish a username and a password. You agree to provide accurate, current and complete information during the registration process and to update such information to keep it accurate, current and complete. You agree not to share your password with any third party. 

### Protection of Minors

Company does not permit children under the age of 13 to register on the PLE Service or use any of its functionality for which registration is required. If you are between the age of 13 and 18 years old, you may use the PLE Service but only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by the KADENZE Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. 

### Personally Identifiable Information (PII)

PII is information that identifies you or can be used to identify, contact, or locate you. For the purpose of the Policy, PII is defined as your name, home or business address, email address, telephone number, and debit or credit card information such as the credit card number or billing address, social media links, personal websites, and grades/evaluations. Company respects your privacy. Company only collects PII through voluntary submissions, such as email, survey information, and online registration forms. The types and amount of PII collected from these activities will vary, but in no event will we collect PII that is not voluntarily given by you when using the PLE Service. You consent to Company using your PII to facilitate requests, to contact you if a problem arises, email you information about our PLE Service, or for other uses consistent with this Policy and your requests. 

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII)

Company collects statistical use data about your use of the PLE. This data does not identify you personally and is purely statistical data, such as monitoring website user traffic, and access patterns. This Non-PII is for your benefit, in order to improve the PLE Service. Such analysis and information is aggregated across viewers, does not identify anyone as an individual and does not link to any PII. 

### Sharing with Third Parties

Company does not share your PII with third parties without your consent except as provided in this Privacy Policy. It may be necessary to share your PII with our trusted business partners, who are bound to confidentiality. Should Company merge with or be acquired by another company, any information collected may be transferred to and used by the resulting company. If Company were to cease operations, your data might be transferred to and used by another company, which offers similar or related products. If such an event occurred, we would attempt to provide you with continuity of PLE Service.  

The PLE Service gives you the ability to share your PII and other User Submissions with other PLE Users. Please consider carefully before disclosing any personal information or data that might be accessible to others. 

Company may share Non-PII with third parties. Be assured that any Non-PII shared does not identify you personally. 

### Grades, Test Assessments and Evaluations

We know your grades, test assessments or evaluations are very important and private to you and we do not share that type of information with any third parties. All grades, test assessments and evaluations are treated as confidential, and such information is available only to the instructors assisting with the grading process and course administration and/or the university or college that is involved. 

### Third Party Links

We may display links, and Users may post links containing content of a third party service or PLE Service. You should always read the privacy policy of a third party service to find out more about how personal information is collected and processed. Company’s Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot fully control how, third parties use your information, and we cannot be held responsible for third parties’ use of your information. 

### Use of IP Addresses

As with any Internet-based service, queries to our PLE Service transmit an Internet Protocol (IP) address, as this is what allows delivery of the information you requested back to you. We also use IP addresses for security purposes and to determine the approximate geographic location (the country or metropolitan region) of the query. We do not use IP addresses to identify an individual user by name, address or exact location. 

### Cookies, Log Information and Opt-Out 

When you are logged into your account, Company sends one or more cookies (which is a small file containing a string of characters) to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. Company uses cookies to give the best experience using the PLE Service. Company servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you log into your user account. These server logs may include information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, please note that if you do this you will not be able to use the full functionality of the PLE Service. You may contact Company at [help@kadenze.com](mailto:help@kadenze.com) for instructions on how to disable cookies. 

### User Communications and Opt-Out

When you send email or other communications to Company, Company may retain those communications and related e-mail addresses in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our PLE Service. In addition, Company may use your username and email address to provide you with PLE news about products and/or PLE Service and information about your user account. If you do not wish to receive these kinds of communications, you may "opt out" by emailing [help@kadenze.com.](mailto:help@kadenze.com)

### Legal Compliance

Company may disclose any information we collect if required to do so by law or under a good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the law or comply with legal process or to protect and defend Company’s rights, property, and customers, whether or not required to do so by law. Company reserves the right to contact appropriate authorities and disclose such information to them at our discretion when it appears that individuals using the PLE Service are engaged in activities that are illegal or violate the KADENZE Terms of Use. 

### Secured Information

Company maintains a variety of physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard your information and to deliver the PLE Service and features of the PLE Service. While Company cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of your data will not occur, Company takes reasonable efforts to prevent such occurrences. 

### Governing Law

This Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of the California without respect to choice of law principles. You agree and submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in Los Angeles, California for resolution of any dispute, action or proceeding in connection with this Agreement. 

### Access to and Deletion of your Personal Information 

In the event you desire to be informed of or access any PII we hold about you, you can email us at [help@kadenze.com.](mailto:help@kadenze.com) You also have the right to delete your PII at any time. Please note, however, that once you delete such information, it may not be recoverable. Once you share any PII with another PLE User, you do not have a chance to recover such information, so carefully consider what information you share. 

### Data Retention

In the event you terminate your account, we may retain basic contact information in the event we need to contact you about your use of the PLE Service. This information is kept strictly confidential. All other PII and Non-PII data may, at Company’s sole discretion, be immediately deleted upon termination of your account. 

### Privacy Policy Updates

Company will update this Privacy Policy as Company’s business and the PLE Service expands and changes. Updates to this Policy will be posted on the PLE website and we will also give you notification of such updates. Your continued use of the PLE Service will constitute consent to the new terms. Company encourages you to review this Policy periodically for any changes that may have been posted. 

### Questions

If you have any questions, comments or feedback about Company’s use of your information or about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [help@kadenze.com.](mailto:help@kadenze.com) Company will use reasonable efforts to promptly investigate any complaint you may have regarding our use of your information.
